DC Showcase: Adam Strange is a animation, action,
science fiction film directed by Butch Lukic.
On a rugged asteroid mining colony, few of the toiling workers are aware that
their town drunk was ever anything but an interplanetary derelict.
But when the miners open a fissure into the home of a horde of
deadly alien insects, his true identity is exposed.
He is space adventurer Adam Strange, whose heroic backstory is played out in flashbacks
as he struggles to save the very people who have scorned him for so long.
Adam Strange (voice), played by Charlie Weber.
Foreman (voice), played by Roger Cross.
Alanna / Diane / Meyra  (voice), played by Kimberly Brooks.
Noris (voice), played by Ray Chase.
Bartender (voice), played by Fred Tatasciore.
DC Showcase: Adam Strange is an American animated short superhero film based
on the character of the same name produced by Warner Bros.
Animation and DC Entertainment.
It was included as part of the home media release of
Justice League Dark: Apokolips War.
The film is also part of the "Tomorrowverse" continuity which begun with Superman:
Man of Tomorrow, and is followed by Green Lantern: Beware My Power.
The film explores themes of superhero, short film,
dc animated movie universe (dcamu).
The tone is thought_provoking.